我们可以通过查看周边来找到描述物体形状的其他信息，
We can find additional information to describe the shape of an object by looking at its perimeter,
通过观察它的边界。在这里，我们有一个非常简单的黑暗场景
by looking at its boundary. Here we have a very simple scene with a dark
反对白色背景的对象。计算周长的最简单方法
object against a white background. The simplest way to compute the length of the perimeter
该对象的目的是简单地跟踪对象的外部。所以线条也是
of the object is to simply trace around the outside of the object. So the lines are either
垂直或水平，这是一种称为裂缝编码的技术。我们测量长度
vertical or horizontal, and this is a technique called crack coding. We measure the length
这条蓝色的道路。它告诉我们一些关于物体周长的信息。
of this blue path. It tells us something about the length of the perimeter of the object.
测量物体周长的另一种方法是首先考虑所有物体
Another way of measuring the perimeter of the object is to first of all consider all
位于对象边缘的像素，并且这些像素都标有
of the pixels that sit on the edge of the object, and those pixels are all marked with
一个红点。那些红点是位于边缘的像素的中心
a red dot. Those red dots are the centres of the pixels that are on the edge of the
宾语。另一种技术是加入点的中心。这就是所谓的
object. And an alternative technique is to join the centres of the dots. This is called
一个8邻居的链码。因此，该路径的长度可以被认为是长度
an 8-neighbour chain code. So the length of this path can be considered to be the length
对象的边界。我们可以看到会有一些
of the boundary of the object. We can see that there are going to be some
差异在这里。破解代码可能会高估其边界
differences here. The crack code is perhaps going to overestimate the boundary of the
宾语。链码可能会低估对象的边界，
object. The chain code is going to perhaps underestimate the boundary of the object,
但是当对象的边缘不是时，链码会做得更好
but the chain code does a much better job when the object has got sides that are neither
垂直也不水平。当对象上有倾斜的段时，链码可能也是如此
vertical nor horizontal. When there are sloped segments on the object, chain code can perhaps
给出一个稍微更现实的估计。在这种情况下，与非常小的对象的差异
give a slightly more realistic estimate. In this case with very small objects the difference
这两种方法之间的关系非常重要。当物体非常大时
between the two approaches is going to be quite significant. When objects are very large
有数百或数千个像素，差异就不那么显着了。
with hundreds or thousands of pixels, the difference is much less significant.
现在，如果我们使用上面提到的任何一种技术计算周长，我们就会调用
Now if we compute the perimeter using either of the techniques just mentioned, and we call
周长p，我们可以计算一个我们称之为圆度的度量
that the perimeter length p, we can compute a measure that we call circularity and this
是一种与紧凑性相关的度量。所以我们取4xπ，乘以面积
is a measure that is related to compactness. So we take 4x π, multiplied by the area of
这个物体来自第0个时刻，我们把它除以周长的平方。
the object, which comes from the zeroth moment, and we divide it by the perimeter squared.
所以这是一个无量纲的数量。分子包含已经获得的区域
So this is a non-dimensional quantity. The numerator contains the area, which has got
像素单位平方。我们除以长度，其中有像素的平方单位。
units of pixels squared. We divided by the length, which has got units of pixels squared.
所以这个无量纲的数量没有单位。
So this non-dimensional quantity has got no units.
对于圆的情况，圆度的值为1...1表示它是圆。
For the case of the circle, circularity has got a value of 1 … 1 means it’s a circle.
小于1意味着它不是一个圆圈，并且它接近一条长线
For less than 1 it means that it’s not a circle, and for a long line it approaches
0，所以它不能大于1，它可以小于1.1如果它是一个圆圈。
0, so it cannot be bigger than 1, it can be less than 1. 1 if it’s a circle.